higher spring fans in this installment
在本期中较高的Spring 风扇
of spring tips we're going to look at
Spring 的技巧，我们将要看
the new features in spring security 5
Spring Security 防护的新功能5
which are designed to support security
旨在支持安全性
in a reactive Spring web flex
在响应式Spring Web Flex中
application so let's create a new demo
应用程序，所以让我们创建一个新的演示
here on start out spring radio we're
在这里开始 Spring 广播，我们
going to use spring boot - dado m2 which
将使用 spring boot -达多M2
is do you know the final release of
您是否知道的最终版本
spring boot is due this December so will
spring boot 定于今年十二月
will take advantage of some of the
将利用一些
milestones here security demo and we're
这里的里程碑安全演示，我们
gonna use the reactive web support now
现在要使用反应式网络支持
at the moment there is no auto
目前没有自动
configuration or starter for spring
Spring 的配置或启动器
security so we will just have to
安全，所以我们只需要
configure it ourselves manually and I
我自己手动配置它
you know I'm using giant ironic air
你知道我在用巨大的讽刺气
quotes here because as you'll see it's
在这里引用是因为您会看到
it's almost trivial how much configures
几乎没有多少配置
and configuration is required to get
和配置是必需的
that to work and then we'll we'll use
工作，然后我们将使用
that to secure a reactive end point so
确保反应性终点
here with our security demo and we'll
这里有我们的安全演示，我们将
point ourselves to that project
将自己指向该项目
descriptor the Maven project descriptor
描述符Maven项目描述符
and open this up in our ide and what
并在我们的思想中打开它，什么
we'll do it as a first cut you know the
我们会首先做的，你知道
first thing we're going to do is build a
我们要做的第一件事是建立一个
simple trivial rest endpoint that
简单琐碎的休息终点
returns a hello world message what else
返回你好世界消息还有什么
right
对
so security demo application and we'll
所以安全演示应用程序，我们将
create a web configuration in point here
在此处创建一个Web配置
and it's gonna be a configuration class
这将是一个配置类
and therein we're gonna define a router
在其中我们要定义一个路由器
function okay so rad functions routes
功能正常，所以rad功能路由
and we'll say return router functions
我们会说返回路由器功能
dot route requests pretty kits dot dot
点路线要求漂亮的套件点
gift for slash message and we're going
斜线消息的礼物，我们要去
to return a new handler function this is
返回一个新的处理函数，这是
the callback that spring web flex is
spring web flex是的回调
expecting us to satisfy in order to
希望我们满意才能
respond to incoming requests so say reso
响应传入的请求，所以说reso
response that okay dot body mono just
响应，好吧，点单声道
hello world and we're gonna tell the
你好，世界，我们要告诉
framework that we're sending back a
我们发回的框架
string okay so let's go ahead and start
字符串好吧，让我们继续并开始
this up now this is a functional
现在，这是一个功能
interface you'll notice that
界面，您会注意到
intelligence telling us it's a function
情报告诉我们这是一个功能
interface and so we could reduce this to
界面，所以我们可以减少到
lambda but for our purposes I think it
lambda，但出于我们的目的，我认为
just makes sense to
才有意义
use method references because functional
使用方法引用是因为功能
interfaces lend themselves to method
接口适用于方法
references just as easily as they do
引用就像他们一样容易
lambda so here I can say this handle and
lambda，所以在这里我可以说这个句柄和
we can refactor this to be called
我们可以将其重构为
message there we are that makes it
消息在那里，我们做到了
cleaner and we can also strip away these
清洁剂，我们也可以去除这些
sort of static import prefixes here that
静态导入前缀在这里
makes it even more clean and
使它更加干净
approachable and there we go so we have
平易近人，我们走了，所以我们有
to we have our code clean up now let's
现在我们清理代码
go ahead and see if it's working curl
来看看它是否正在卷曲
HTTP localhost 8080 forward slash
HTTP localhost 8080正斜杠
message there's our simple message now
消息，现在有我们的简单消息
the message is interesting but let's
该消息很有趣，但让我们
contextualize it that's a you know
情境化这就是你知道的
personalize it just a little bit we know
个性化一点我们知道
once we add security that we you know
一旦我们添加了您知道的安全性
we'll know who would user it is so let's
我们会知道谁会使用它，所以让我们
add security and then we'll well
增加安全性，然后我们会好的
personalize the message to reflect the
个性化消息以反映
currently authenticated user so to add
当前经过身份验证的用户，因此要添加
security we need to bring in the three
我们需要引入三个安全性
dependencies that comprise the core of
构成核心的依赖项
the spring security web flex support so
Spring Security Web Flex支持如此
we say spring security config and we
我们说Spring Security 配置，我们
don't have to manage the versions
不必管理版本
thankfully that's already done for us
幸运的是，这已经为我们完成了
spring boot five spring blue two rather
spring boot 五春蓝色二颇
has from security five you know
从安全上有五个你知道
configured and managed for us in the
在中为我们配置和管理
version ranges so that's just just a
版本范围，所以只是一个
simple chore bring in the core support
简单的琐事带来核心支持
the web flex support and the config
Web Flex支持和配置
support and with that we need to teach
支持，我们需要教
spring security how to answer the
Spring Security 如何回答
requirement of authentication and
认证要求
authorization so first we'll do
授权，所以我们首先要做
authentication we'll say security
身份验证，我们称之为安全性
security configuration and we're going
安全配置，我们要
to make this a configuration class I'm
使它成为配置类
going to activate the web flex security
要激活Web Flex安全性
support in there and then you know
支持在那里，然后你知道
springing web flux just like spring seek
Spring 弹力通量就像Spring 搜索
the spring security with spring mukluks
Spring Mukluks的Spring Security
just like traditional spring security
就像传统的Spring Security
has at its heart the concept of an
其核心是
authentication manager and it can in
身份验证管理器，它可以在
turn delegate to a reactor until a user
将代表转到反应堆，直到用户
details repository which more or less
详细信息存储库，或多或少
corresponds to a doubt authentication
对应于疑问认证
provider in the traditional spring
传统 Spring 的提供者
security world and it in turn is
安全世界，反过来又是
responsible for answering requests that
负责回答要求
are you know authentication requests
你知道认证请求吗
that are done
完成了
terms of use names and passwords so we
使用条款名称和密码，因此我们
can provide a very simple reactive
可以提供非常简单的反应
friendly user details repository here
友好的用户详细信息存储库
that has just a few inbuilt users and
只有几个内置用户，
passwords right and we can configure
密码正确，我们可以配置
this using the map user details
使用地图用户详细信息
repository we're not talking to a proper
我们没有与适当的存储库交谈
identity provider here nothing like LDAP
身份提供者这里没有LDAP
or Active Directory or something like
或Active Directory或类似的东西
that for now because we just want to
现在，因为我们只想
demonstrate what it looks like to to
展示它看起来像什么
make this work behind the suite behind
使这项工作在后面的套件后面
the scene Springs Security's gonna
Springs Security的现场
create an authentication manager for you
为您创建一个身份验证管理器
that uses this user details repository
使用此用户详细信息存储库
so we don't have to do any of that
所以我们不需要做任何事情
wiring if we don't want to now we need a
如果我们现在不想接线，我们需要一个
few years users of course so let's
几年的用户，当然，让我们
create a username forge a long a user
创建用户名伪造一个用户
forge a long the role of course is just
锻造一个很长的角色当然只是
user and the password of course is
用户，密码当然是
password because of course it is right
密码，因为它当然是正确的
so there's that and we'll create the
这样就可以了，我们将创建
jail on user and I'll just duplicate
对用户入狱，我将重复
this to create our winches user and our
这将创建我们的绞车用户和我们的
winch of course is Rob winch the lead of
绞盘当然是Rob绞盘的领先者
the spring security project and I'm sure
Spring Security 项目，我确定
he would love it if you grab the bits
如果你抓住一点他会喜欢的
and try it out some of the stuff we're
并尝试一些我们
talking about here and fed back so
在这里谈论并反馈
please do so jail on our winch those are
请在我们的绞车上这样做，
two users and what this is gonna do this
两个用户，这将要做什么
default configuration with this
默认配置与此
annotation and this one being this is
注释，这是这个
going to lock down everything and
要锁定一切，
restrict access to any resources no
限制对任何资源的访问
matter what the name of the resource
不管资源的名称是什么
assuming that request is authenticated
假设该请求已通过身份验证
and we can see that here let's just
我们可以看到这里
restart the application and we'll turn
重新启动应用程序，我们将转向
on verbose logging here for the curl
在这里详细记录卷曲
call and you can see it says 401
打电话，您会看到它说401
unauthorized and I can now authorize
未经授权，我现在可以授权
myself by saying jail on call and
通过在通话中说入狱和
password that's my username and password
密码就是我的用户名和密码
there's the message however impersonal
有消息，但是不个人
so let's now personalize the message
现在让我们个性化消息
we'll take this a bit further will say
我们将进一步说明
server request dot principal P hello
服务器请求点主体P你好
Pete
皮特
name right so P dot o principal
名称正确，因此P点或主体
that map p dot get name extra
该地图p点获得额外的名称
exclamation marks right so there's this
感叹号正确，所以有这个
and we'll save principal publisher okay
这样我们就可以保存主要发布者了
so I'm gonna use that principal
所以我要用那个校长
publisher instead of the default one
发布者，而不是默认发布者
that we've just provided before but the
我们刚刚提供的，但是
results should basically what we expect
结果基本上应该是我们期望的
so let's go ahead and restart this see
所以让我们继续并重新开始看看
the results so if I make them make the
结果，所以如果我让他们做
call now
现在打电话
it says hello jail all right there's the
它说你好监狱好吧
respawn Stan there and that's working
重生斯坦在那里，这是工作
that's working as we expect if I
如果我期望的话，那是我们期望的
authenticate as our Lynch our winch I
将我们的绞盘鉴定为我们的Lynch
get a hello our winch so it's clearly
打个招呼吧，很明显
aware of the of the the other thing to
意识到另一件事
get principal now we can do something a
现在获得校长，我们可以做点什么
little more interesting now we can look
有趣一点，现在我们可以看看
at authorization right and in so doing
在授权的情况下，这样做
we have to prescribe the default
我们必须规定默认
authorization for all the other end
另一端的授权
points that right now spring security is
指出现在的Spring Security 是
doing for us right so the default
对我们来说是正确的，所以默认
behavior here is that if we just do
这里的行为是，如果我们只是这样做
authentication and we don't provide any
身份验证，我们不提供任何身份验证
any ideas as to how it should do
关于应该怎么做的任何想法
authorization it'll just lock down
授权它只会锁定
everything we can be a little more
我们可以多做一点
specific but we have to now make sure to
具体的，但我们现在必须确保
cover the ground that we gained that we
掩盖我们获得的基础
that we gain by not specifying this
我们通过不指定这个来获得
manually we we have to read we claim
手动，我们必须阅读我们的声明
that that ground because uh once we
那个地面，因为呃，一旦我们
exert some control over one one route
对一条路线施加控制
one end point spring Security's going to
Spring Security 性的一个终点
expect us to provide authorization for
希望我们为以下事项提供授权
all of it right for all the end points
所有这些都适合所有终点
otherwise it'll just leave it as default
否则，将其保留为默认值
so let's create a beam here a security
所以让我们在这里创建一个光束
web filter chain we're just gonna call
网络过滤器链，我们只是要打电话
this the security endpoint I'm gonna
这是我要使用的安全性端点
inject the spring security HTTP security
注入spring安全HTTP安全
DSL there and we'll say build there's
DSL在那里，我们会说在那里建造
our DSL what we're gonna say is we're
我们的DSL，我们要说的是
gonna say authorize exchange thought any
要说授权交流想什么
exchange is authenticated right and
交换是经过验证的权利，
there we are so that's our first bit of
我们在那里，这是我们的第一点
configuration that should be where we
配置应该是我们在哪里
were before basically it's gonna require
基本上之前是需要
that everything be authenticated let's
一切都经过验证，让我们
see if that works
看看是否可行
okay so there's hello Rob Lynch but if
好吧，罗伯·林奇问好
we tamper with a password
我们篡改密码
it doesn't let's go through its
它不让我们经历它的
unauthorized that would seem to
未经授权，似乎
tell us that everything's working as
告诉我们一切都在
before so hello world there we go
在你好世界之前，我们去了
now let's create a new endpoint that
现在让我们创建一个新的端点
will serve up the information and serve
将提供信息并服务
up the authentication information about
验证有关的信息
the currently authenticated user as JSON
当前经过身份验证的用户为JSON
back to the client but we don't want you
回到客户，但我们不希望您
know the client to be able to talk or to
知道客户能够交谈或与
see other people's information right
正确查看他人的信息
we're going to limit the access to other
我们将限制对其他人的访问
principal information to just the
主要信息
username implied by the authentication
身份验证隐含的用户名
so let's create an endpoint here that
所以我们在这里创建一个端点
says get forward slash users forward
说前进大幅削减用户前进
slash username right and here again
右击斜杠用户名，然后再次在此处
we're just get a new handler like so and
我们只是得到一个像这样的新处理程序
I'll say that this handler is called
我会说这个处理程序叫做
username and all we're gonna do in this
用户名以及我们要做的一切
handler name and this handler it is we
处理程序名称，这个处理程序是我们
turn the JSON information right for the
将JSON信息向右转
for the current principal so the
对于当前的本金，所以
principal is a Java security principle
主体是Java安全原则
but that's not what we want we know that
但这不是我们想要的，我们知道
behind the scenes that principal is
幕后那个校长是
actually a authentication object so
实际上是一个认证对象
let's get rid of this because we know
让我们摆脱这个，因为我们知道
that this isn't gonna be the same type
不会是同一类型
anymore so we're gonna say
不再，所以我们要说
authentication class dot cast
认证类点播
P and then we know that the principal
P，然后我们知道
object is going to be a user details
对象将成为用户详细信息
that's the very same user details that
这是与用户详细信息相同的
we've just persisted in our repository a
我们只是坚持在我们的存储库
few minutes ago so we'll turn that into
几分钟前，我们将其变成
a user details and there we are there's
用户详细信息，我们在那里
our user - details reference we can
我们的用户-详细信息，我们可以
dereference that to a details mano and
取消引用细节手册
maybe clean that up a little there we go
也许清理一点，我们去
so now well put that their details mano
所以现在把它们的细节放进去
and we'll tell this the runtime that
我们将告诉运行时
this is a user details object that
这是一个用户详细信息对象，
should be treated as such
应该这样对待
and let's just confirm that that works
让我们确认一下是否可行
before we dive into authorization let's
在我们深入研究授权之前，让我们
dive into let's just make sure that this
深入研究，只需确保
is working as we expect so users are
正在按照我们的预期工作，因此用户
winch
绞车
there we are there's our information
那里我们有我们的信息
there's the same information for J long
J long有相同的信息
and what we want to do is when a limit
我们想要做的是
you know the authenticated user from
您知道来自的经过身份验证的用户
accessing information that doesn't
访问不存在的信息
belong to that authenticated user so
属于该经过身份验证的用户，因此
we're gonna do authorization in effect
我们将进行有效的授权
on that end point on that URL so we do
在那个URL的那个端点上，所以我们
that here in our security configuration
在我们的安全配置中
we go back to our security configuration
我们回到安全配置
here and we say that for requests going
在这里，我们说对于要求去
to a certain path users for slash
到某个路径用户进行斜杠
username we want the following access
用户名，我们需要以下访问权限
decisions to apply right and we have we
决定申请权利，我们拥有
could by the way we could say that any
可以顺便说一句
request that comes in has to be
传入的请求必须是
authenticated that's basically what we
经过验证的基本上就是我们
did before we could say it has to have a
在我们可以说它必须有一个之前
certain Authority or a certain role but
某个权威或某个角色，但
one of the new features in spring
Spring 的新功能之一
security 5 is since it's based on Java
安全5是因为它基于Java
Java 8 and and spring 5 is itself also
Java 8和Spring 5本身也是
based on Java 8 we can take advantage of
基于Java 8，我们可以利用
lambdas so this is very convenient now
lambdas，所以现在非常方便
access call back here where we might
在此处访问我们的电话
have had two previously use a spring
曾经有两次使用Spring
expression language expression to do the
表达语言表达
sort of same dynamic control we can now
我们现在可以进行相同的动态控制
do that here which is by providing a new
在这里这样做是通过提供一个新的
reactive authorization manager so
被动授权经理
reactive authorization manager and this
反应授权管理器和这个
should be all that heart right we're
我们应该全心全意
gonna say that we're gonna you know
要说我们会知道
we're gonna check the incoming request
我们将检查传入的请求
which has an authentication in it this
里面有一个认证
is already after the users been
用户访问过之后
authenticated and we're gonna you know
已通过身份验证，我们会知道
figure out the name of the authenticated
找出已验证的名称
user and then see if it matches the URL
用户，然后查看它是否与URL相匹配
against which we're making the request
我们针对之提出要求
right so it's the the context here has
对，这就是这里的背景
the current username so we're gonna say
当前的用户名，所以我们要说
mano dot map and off-off dot dot get
mano点图和off-off点点get
name equals context thought get
名称等于上下文认为得到
variables dot get username right so
变量dot获取用户名正确，因此
that's a boolean and we need to map that
这是一个布尔值，我们需要将其映射
boolean into something called an
布尔值称为
authorization decision so there's a
授权决定，所以有一个
constructor that just takes a boolean so
只需一个布尔值的构造函数
we can just use a method reference like
我们可以像这样使用方法引用
so right
好吧
okay there's our authorization check and
好的，有我们的授权检查和
of course this is a functional interface
当然这是一个函数式接口
as well so we can replace that
也可以替换掉
accordingly and the code gets very nice
因此，代码变得非常漂亮
to read write very clean
读写写很干净
write very easy to follow what's
写得很容易遵循
happening and we get type safety here
发生，我们在这里获得类型安全
it's a spring expression language so
这是一种 Spring Expression Language ，所以
that can be very very useful if you're
如果您是
trying to figure out the chain of
试图找出链
invocation all right so let's see if
调用好吧，让我们看看
that works now notice that we're doing
现在可以正常工作，请注意我们正在做
this specific thing before we do the
在执行此特定操作之前，
more broadly applicable thing down here
这里更广泛适用的东西
right we're we're saying first check
对，我们是说第一张支票
this very specific pattern and then if
这个非常具体的模式，然后如果
it doesn't match anything in these these
这些都不符合
paths that we specify any any number of
我们指定任意数量的路径
paths or predicates that we specify then
我们指定的路径或predicate
use this one here and say that for any
在这里使用这个说任何
request into the service into the
请求进入服务
application there they should be
他们应该在那里
authenticated right so let's see now if
正确的身份验证，让我们现在看看
that works okay so I'm authentic ated
可以，所以我很满意
right now I'm going to authenticate it
现在我要进行身份验证
as our winch if I'm going to talk to
如果我要和我们聊天的话
jail all right and it says 403 forbidden
没事的监狱，它说禁止403
now what about our winch there we are so
现在我们的绞盘怎么样
I've now accessed the information
我现在已经访问了信息
specific to our winch and of course I've
特定于我们的绞车，当然我已经
got my message endpoint as well so
也得到了我的消息端点
there's a hello our winch so with that
你好，我们的绞盘，所以
we've looked at spring security five
我们看过Spring Security 五
there's a lot of really cool stuff here
这里有很多很棒的东西
I've just touched on the integration for
我刚刚谈到了
securing a basic web application using H
使用H保护基本的Web应用程序
to be basic but of course you'll see a
是基本的，但当然您会看到
number of different protocols and
不同协议的数量和
technology support and spring security
技术支持和Spring 安全
as usual one of which of course is
与往常一样，其中之一当然是
oo-oo-oo officer has been previously
oo-oo-oo官员以前是
addressed in previously supported by the
在以前由
spring cloud security and spring
spring-cloud-security和 Spring
security oauth projects themselves the
安全oauth会自行计划
spring security olaf project is now
Spring Security 奥拉夫项目现在
being folded into spring security five
被折叠成Spring Security 五
so you'll see that out of the box
这样您就可以立即看到
supported and interactive fashion in
支持和交互方式
spring security 5 itself all right with
Spring Security 5本身可以
that thanks very much for watching and
非常感谢您的观看和
we'll see you next time
下次见
you
您